<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>akrehl | Projects &amp; Blog</title>
    <link>https://akrehl.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on akrehl | Projects &amp; Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-EN</language>
    <copyright>(c) 2016 Adrian Krehl</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 May 2016 11:39:55 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://akrehl.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://akrehl.com/2016/05/26/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2016 11:39:55 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akrehl.com/2016/05/26/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello World!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you will find something valuable for you on my site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for passing by!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://akrehl.com/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2016 11:34:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akrehl.com/project/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The speed of development and innovations on the web platform, at the time of writing, is enormous.
There are a number of new things we all heard of. I am following some of them with detail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not YET an active part of the open source community, but this will change!
I already have some ideas on my todo list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All my future projects will be listed here.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributions</title>
      <link>https://akrehl.com/contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2016 11:17:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akrehl.com/contribution/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Currently I am very busy and have not started to give back to the wonderful open source community.
I am actively watching some interesting projects I would like to contribute to in the near future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All my valuable contributions in the future will be listed here.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://akrehl.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 17:08:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akrehl.com/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m Adrian Krehl and currently a student in applied computer science at the Hochschule Hannover, Germany.
Additionally I am working in a small software company. I love technology and coding in a variety of languages both at
work and in my spare time. When I’m not coding, I try to spend time with my family and friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-this-site-is-about-and-what-not&#34;&gt;What this site is about and what not&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did make this site for my own purpose. Mainly for giving me a good platform for testing and sharing new ideas and code
with the community. I do not want to label the site to any specific topic or programming language. I am just to
interested in all of them 😃 . I consider myself a beginner in software engineering, so please do not copy and
paste any code without a closer look. Take a look at my &lt;a href=&#34;https://akrehl.com/license.txt&#34;&gt;license&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you may already noticed, I am not a native english speaker. Please be kind, I give my very best!
Opinions are my own and not the views of my employer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>